欢迎来到我们的在线课程“机器人入门”的第一堂课。
Welcome to the very first lecture in our online course, Introduction to Robotics.
我的名字是PeterCorke，我将在接下来的六周内成为你的讲师。
My name is Peter Corke and I’ll be your lecturer for the next six weeks.
所以，如果您喜欢虚构的基础，这是一个非常快速的过程
So, this is a really quick run through if you like the, the fictional underpinnings
机器人技术我们在第一期课程中要做的就是看看各种各样的
of robotics. What we’re going do in this first course is look at the great variety
今天存在的机器人我们将从制造机器人开始。这些
of robots that exist today. We’re going start off with manufacturing robots. These
你看到的手臂式机器人是在建造汽车，建造电脑的工厂里工作的
are the arm type robots that you see working in factories building cars, building computers
等等，非常非常重要的一类机器人。而且，这就是我们要去的机器人类型
and so on, very, very important class of robots. And, that’s the type of robot we are going
在本机器人入门课程中最仔细地学习。但是，在这个特别的
to study most carefully in this Introduction to Robotics course. But, in this particular
讲座，我想描绘出不同类型的机器人的大局
lecture, I want to paint the big picture of the different types of robots that are in
今天的世界。所以，我们将看看驾驶的机器人，飞行的机器人，机器人
the world today. So, we are going to look at robots that drive, robots that fly, robots
在水下游泳或在水面上划桨的机器人，
that swim underneath the water or robots that paddle around on the surface of the water,
有效的机器人船。所以，在这第一堂课中，我们将会这样做
effectively robotic boats. So, in this first lecture, we are going to
让我们了解机器人技术的巨大传播。然后，剩下的
orient ourselves in learning about the big spread of robotics. And then, for the remainder
当然，我们要特别关注臂式机器人。
of the course, we are going to knuckle down and look at arm type robots in particular.